halfwayanywhere.com 2017-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Halfway Anywhere

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read this privacy policy to get a clear understanding of how I collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information.

**What personal information do I collect from visitors?**  
When visiting the site you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to subscribe to regular updates.

**When do I collect information?**  
I collect information from you when you subscribe to my newsletter or enter information on the site.

**How do I use your information?**  
I may use the information collected from you when you sign up for my newsletter in the following ways:

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

**How do I protect visitor information?**  
I do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. I only provide articles and information. I will never ask for sensitive information such as credit card numbers.  
I use regular Malware Scanning.  
I do not use an SSL certificate because I only provide articles and information and never ask for sensitive information such as credit card numbers.

**Does the website use ‘cookies'?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help to remember previous selections you've made on the site. I also use cookies to help compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that I can offer a better site experiences and tools in the future. I also use cookies to keep track of advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies, it won't affect your user experience.

**Third-party disclosure**  
I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. However, **third-party links** are occasionally included to offer third-party products or services on the website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of my site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by [Google's Advertising Principles](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en). They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

I use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**I have implemented the following:** Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Demographics and Interests Reporting. I, along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to my website.

**Opting out:** Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act** CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. See more [here](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf).

**According to CalOPPA I agree to the following:**

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our homepage or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * My Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
  * Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.
  * Users are able to change their personal information by emailing me.

**How does my site handle do not track signals?**  
I honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does my site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**  
It's also important to note that we I not allow third-party behavioral tracking **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**. When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 18, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

**I do not specifically market to children under 18.**

**Fair Information Practices**  
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: I will notify the users via email within 7 business days.

I also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**  
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM I agree to the following:**

  * NOT to use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify messages as advertisements in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of my business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email me at contact@halfwayanywhere.com or simply follow the instructions at the bottom of each email to be promptly removed from **ALL** correspondence.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

HalfwayAnywhere.com  
7915 Ruffner Ave.  
Van Nuys, CA 91406  
USA  
contact@halfwayanywhere.com

Last Edited on 2016-05-12
